hello thank you for coming here this
你好，谢谢你来到这里
morning my name is Joe Darcy I work in
早上我叫乔·达西，我在这里工作
Oracle's Java platform group and I'll be
Oracle的Java平台小组，我将成为
talking today about JDK 9 language
今天谈论JDK 9语言
tooling and library features if we don't
工具和库功能，如果我们不这样做
get to your questions at the end or if
最后回答您的问题，或者
you're watching the talk on streaming
您正在观看有关流媒体的演讲
you can tweet questions the hashtag on
您可以在以下标签发布问题标签：
the first slide here getting a 9 Lang's
第一张幻灯片在这里得到9郎的
tools libs this is a very important
工具库，这是非常重要的
slide from Oracle's lawyers they want
他们想要的甲骨文律师的幻灯片
you to make sure to not put too much
你要确保不要放太多
trust in what I have to say here during
相信我在此期间必须说的话
during this talk this is the safe harbor
在这次谈话中，这是安全港
slide I must say though if you're
幻灯片，我必须说，如果你是
interested in safe harbors there are
对安全港感兴趣
many other safe harbors in the Bay Area
湾区许多其他安全港
or you to visit so please especially if
或您来拜访，所以特别是如果
it's your first time here please make
这是你第一次来
sure to check out some of these other
一定要检查其中一些
safe harbors in the area quick survey
该地区的安全港快速调查
which JDK 9 release are using now in
现在正在使用哪个JDK 9版本
production to show of hands JDK nine
生产展示之手JDK九
early access which cutting edge dig saw
抢先体验哪个最先进的挖锯
a few people using that that's good
一些人使用那很好
about the other JDK 9 builds the usual
关于其他JDK 9构建通常的
ones it's good to put these in your CI
最好将这些放在您的CI中
systems now to see how your your
系统现在看看您的
products work with the upcoming builds
产品可与即将推出的产品一起使用
JDK 8 good it's good to see strong
JDK 8很好，很高兴看到强大
adoption JDK 8 people still on 7 ah
通过JDK 8人还在7啊
maybe 15-20 percent or so 6 still some
可能是15％到20％左右6
hands 4 6 I now admit it who is on 5 or
hand 4 6我现在承认是谁在5或
older anyone ok we have a few brave
老年人，好吧，我们有些勇敢
souls will admit hopefully after this
灵魂将在此之后希望
talk and others you'll you'll have more
交谈和其他人，您将拥有更多
motivation to try to update to some of
尝试更新某些内容的动机
the newer day decays we've had since
从那以后我们开始衰落
then an overview of JDK 9 current
然后是JDK 9的概述
schedule released next year in July as I
我明年七月发布的时间表
mentioned the early access bills are
提到提早进入账单是
already available there's a one main
已经有一个主要的
lease line of development and a second
租赁开发线和第二条
one for jigsaw that's a little more
一个拼图，还有一点
farther out for that product JDK 9 is
对于该产品，JDK 9的更远版本是
being developed under the auspices of
在...的主持下发展
open JDK so if you're interested in
打开JDK，所以如果您有兴趣
following the development as it goes
跟上发展的步伐
along
沿
there are mailing lists and projects so
有邮件列表和项目，所以
you can get the source code there's also
您可以获取源代码
the option group if you want some help
选项组，如果您需要帮助
getting started with JDK 9 part of the
JDK 9入门
adoption group
收养小组
is also an outreach to various open
也是各种开放的延伸
source projects to have them run their
源项目以使它们运行
test Suites and their products with JDK
JDK测试套件及其产品
9 to give us more feedback sooner about
9为我们尽快提供更多反馈
how other software products in the
其他软件产品如何
ecosystem I work with 9 along the way
我一直与9合作的生态系统
throughout the rest of the talk I'll be
在接下来的演讲中，我将
using term jep for a jdk enhancement
使用术语jep进行jdk增强
proposal these are a document to use for
提案这些是用于的文件
project tracking now and dhoop needs you
项目跟踪现在，dhoop需要您
yes--you to help out in try your java
是的-您可以帮助您尝试使用Java
programs with jdk 9 please let us know
jdk 9的程序，请告诉我们
how it goes so we can make any
怎么样，所以我们可以做任何
provements before GA next year now as
明年GA之前的证明现在为
you've no doubt heard modularity is the
您无疑听说过模块化是
big feature coming coming in JDK 9 in
JDK 9中引入了一项重大功能
project jigsaw and in a nutshell
概述项目拼图
modularity lets you group together
模块化使您可以组合在一起
groups of packages in a unit with
单位中的包装组
stronger encapsulation than you find in
比您发现的更强大的封装
a jar file now this is a very pervasive
一个jar文件，这是一个非常普遍的
change to the platform we're changing
改变我们要改变的平台
the language there are new module info
语言中有新的模块信息
files that allow you to declare the
允许您声明的文件
dependencies between modules and other
模块与其他模块之间的依赖性
aspects of the modules so that means we
模块的各个方面，这意味着我们
have to modify the Java C command to
必须修改Java C命令以
recognize the new source files we also
识别新的源文件，我们也
have to update the runtime command Java
必须更新运行时命令Java
to recognize the modules and there's
识别模块，并且
also updates to core reflection and
还更新了核心反射和
things like that so we would have to do
这样的事情，所以我们必须做
those set of changes for many like
对许多人来说，那些变化
larger language changes such as lambda
较大的语言更改，例如lambda
would have to change those as well but
也将不得不改变那些，但
with modularity it's also a change to
有了模块化，这也是对
the programming model so it's really a
编程模型，所以它实际上是一个
much more pervasive change than many of
比许多其他方法更普遍的变化
the changes we've seen previously to
我们之前看到的变化
Java so the modularity work wouldn't fit
Java，因此模块化工作不适合
all in one talk the jigsaw teams
拼图拼图团队
actually giving 5 talks here at JavaOne
实际上在JavaOne上进行了5个演讲
most of them are given twice there's
他们大多数都给了两次
some of them starting later this
他们中的一些人稍后开始
afternoon in this very room so if you
下午在这个房间里，如果你
want to head out and come back in later
想出去然后再回来
on you can get caught up with jigsaw
在上面你会被拼图困扰
there's also a hack session later in the
稍后还会有一个黑客会议
week after some brief notes about our
关于我们的一些简短笔记后一周
stewardship of Java there's three main
Java的管理主要有以下三个方面
areas we'll be talking about for first
我们首先要讨论的领域
to note though that JDK 9 even without
需要注意的是，即使没有
jigsaw is a significant release it's
拼图是一个重要的版本
very large
很大
just to give some scope here's a quick
只是为了给一些范围，这里是一个快速
graph of the bug counts in 8 vs 9 so
图中的错误计数为8 vs 9，因此
basically since the beginning we've had
基本上从一开始就
a higher bug fix rate in 9 min &amp; 8 so it
9分钟和8分钟内的错误修复率更高，因此
is a very significant release even
甚至是非常重要的版本
without jigsaw and we'll be talking
没有拼图，我们会谈
about the non modularity features in
关于中的非模块化功能
this talk today you can group those
今天的演讲，您可以将这些分组
features in three basic areas tool
三个基本领域工具的功能
improvements language libraries the
改进语言库
features don't always align neatly with
功能并不总是与整齐地对齐
these divisions so we that's not a
这些部门，所以我们不是
stretch division how to talk and if we
伸展师怎么说话，如果我们
have some time at the end we'll do you a
最后有一些时间，我们将为您做一个
so first a quick note on stewardship now
因此，现在先简要介绍一下管理
the approach the stewardship we use in
我们使用的管理方法
the JDK is not the sort of stewardship
JDK不是那种管家
we saw by Denethor and Lord of the Rings
我们由Denethor和《指环王》看到
films it's much more benign actually
电影实际上更加良性
under Oracle the main priority of the
在Oracle下，
Java platform group has been to keep
Java平台组一直保持
Java vibrant that's been our consistent
Java充满活力，这是我们始终如一的
priority over the years and that
这些年来的优先事项
influences the approach we use to
影响我们使用的方法
evolving the platform so this is written
不断发展的平台，所以写
up in this document the open JDK
在本文档中打开JDK
developer's guide part of keeping Java
保留Java的开发者指南部分
vibrant is for the most part keeping the
在大多数情况下，充满活力
things that work today working tomorrow
今天工作的事情明天工作
there are exceptions to that of course
当然有例外
but that's that's the default in more
但这是更多情况下的默认设置
detail what that means in technical
详细说明技术上的含义
terms is that we want to preserve
条款是我们要保留
compatibility and there are different
兼容性和有不同
kinds of compatibility you can talk
您可以谈论的各种兼容性
about first is binary compatibility
首先是二进制兼容性
that's the fun in the JLS as they can
他们可以在JLS中获得乐趣
continue the ability to link so when
继续链接的能力，所以当
Java goes to the run your jar file or
Java运行您的jar文件或
other artifact you can still link it and
您仍然可以链接其他工件，并且
get it started
开始吧
there's source incompatibilities does
存在源不兼容性
your code still compile if it's still
您的代码仍然可以编译
compiled does it compile to a program
编译是否编译为程序
that means a class file that means the
这意味着一个类文件，这意味着
same thing
一样
and finally there's behavioral
最后有行为
compatibilities what does your code
兼容性您的代码是什么
actually do do at runtime so we want to
实际上是在运行时做的，所以我们想
keep all of these in mind this informs
请牢记所有这些，这会告知
our language evolution too we want to
我们的语言也在发展
make sure to keep recognizing the old
确保继续认识旧的
class file so you don't have to recreate
类文件，因此您不必重新创建
your jars to new versions of the
您的罐子到新版本的
platform we want to limit the cases
我们要限制案件的平台
where ode cold doesn't compile anymore
不再冷的地方
with the new language version and we
使用新的语言版本，我们
don't want to introduce silent changes
不想引入沉默的变化
and how Java C generates code for the
以及Java C如何为
most part and that is supposed to be a
大部分，这应该是一个
three dimensional graph but you can't
三维图，但是你不能
see the axes on the display there okay
看到显示器上的轴好了
but just imagine it's a grid four source
但只要想象这是一个网格四源
binary behavioral layout like you might
像你可能的二进制行为布局
see in physics class so this
在物理课上看到这样
compatibility policy differs for
兼容性政策因
different releases with the
与不同的版本
implementation of a differs so if we
a的实现方式不同，因此如果我们
have every release like the quarterly
每个季度都有发布
security updates that come out every few
每隔几个出现的安全更新
months we want to have a very small
几个月我们想拥有一个很小的
compatibility impact in that kind of
这种兼容性的影响
release so we might have something
释放，所以我们可能会有一些东西
that's limited to the source behavioral
这仅限于源行为
plane so we have one a little bit of
飞机，所以我们有一点
behavior compatibility we don't want the
行为兼容性，我们不希望
exploits to work anymore for fixing your
利用漏洞修复您的漏洞
security issue maybe a tad of source
安全问题可能源源不绝
competive source incompatibility if we
如果我们存在竞争性来源不兼容
have a larger update release something
有更大的更新版本
like 8u 20 or @u 40 we have a little
像8u 20或@u 40，我们有一点
more room to maneuver a little more
更大的回旋余地
leeway to make behavioral changes
进行行为改变的余地
because it's a large release but still
因为它是一个大版本，但仍然
not too much source compatibility and in
没有太多的源兼容性和
both of these cases no binary
这两种情况都没有二进制
compatibility change we don't want
我们不需要的兼容性更改
people to not have the ability to link
人们没有联系的能力
on the program if we have a feature
在程序上，如果我们有一个功能
release like JDK 8 or especially JDK 9
像JDK 8或特别是JDK 9发行
there's more room we are we will make
我们将有更多的空间
larger behavioral changes in some cases
在某些情况下会有较大的行为改变
will make source battle changes in with
将与
an up justification we will make binary
一个向上的证明，我们将使二进制
incompatible changes in a release like 8
版本8中不兼容的更改
or 9 so let's give an example to help
或9，所以让我们举个例子来帮助
illustrate how this policy works in
说明此政策的运作方式
practice this is the specification for
实践这是针对
hash map buff iterator returns an
哈希图buff迭代器返回一个
iterator and particularly out here the
迭代器，尤其是在这里
elements are returned in no particular
元素没有特别的返回
order
订购
that means a correct program should not
这意味着正确的程序不应该
rely on the order of the elements
依靠元素的顺序
returned by the iterator so that's
由迭代器返回，因此
allowed by so if we want in the
如果我们想要在
implementation to change this order
实施以更改此订单
that's allowed by the spec so going
规范允许这样做
through the different kinds of
通过不同的
compatibility that's binary compatible
二进制兼容的兼容性
there's the same set of methods so
有相同的方法集
nothing's changing there its source
那里什么都没有改变
compatible for the same reasons you know
出于相同的原因兼容
nothing that would affect the source
没有任何会影响来源的东西
code is changing however it is a change
代码正在更改，但是这是更改
in the behavior compatibility and we
在行为兼容性上，我们
know that people can and do rely on the
知道人们可以并且确实依靠
iteration order sometimes even our tests
迭代顺序有时甚至是我们的测试
rely on the iteration order then we have
依靠迭代顺序，那么我们有
to fix the test
修复测试
so this kind of change generally
所以这种变化通常
wouldn't be allowed in either kind of
在任何一种情况下都不允许
update release but it can be and has
更新版本，但可以并且具有
been made in a feature release like 8 or
是在功能发布（例如8或
9 so when you update to new JDK or
9，所以当您更新到新的JDK或
perhaps as you've already updated to JDK
也许因为您已经更新到JDK
8 we use this binary source behavioral
8我们使用这种二进制源行为
compatibility documentation in the
兼容性文档
release notes and compatibility guide
发行说明和兼容性指南
reproduce for the JDK release so he the
复制为JDK版本，所以他
slides will have a link to the guide for
幻灯片将具有指向该指南的链接
eight a particular note if you've
如果有的话，要注意八点
updated 8 you might have already run
更新了8您可能已经运行
into this the order of methods returns
方法的顺序返回
by class yet methods changed in JDK 8 so
按类，但方法在JDK 8中已更改，因此
if you had a unit test for lolling on
如果您要进行单元测试
that you have to have update them and
您必须对其进行更新，
later in nine time frame will produce a
在九个时间段的后期会产生一个
similar document for JDK 9 and if this
JDK 9的类似文档，如果这
sort of discussion about compatibility
关于兼容性的讨论
interest you there's a talk by Ian
感兴趣，你有Ian的演讲
Robertson later in the conference about
罗伯逊稍后在会议上谈到
the science and art of backwards
落后的科学与艺术
compatibility ian is in the audience but
兼容性ian在观众中，但是
the since this is in the keynote we
因为这是我们的主题演讲
won't have them come up and do a walk on
不会让他们站起来继续前进
so how is JDK 9 different from other
那么JDK 9与其他有什么不同
platform releases with modularity coming
即将发布的模块化产品
because it's a large feature and it's
因为这是一个很大的功能，而且
one that we think is necessary to keep
我们认为有必要保留的一种
Java vibrant for the next 21 years
未来21年Java充满活力
there's a larger compatibilities a
有更大的兼容性
larger set of changes will make to
更大的变化将使
compatibility more so than usual for
兼容性比平常更
example in terms of behavioral
行为方面的例子
compatibility we're making changes even
兼容性，我们甚至在做出改变
in the layout of the file so there is no
在文件的布局中，因此没有
RT jar and JDK 9 so if you have some
RT jar和JDK 9，如果有的话
process that relies or assumes RT jar
依赖或假定RT jar的过程
will be there it's not anymore and
会在那里，不再了，
you'll have to update that so that's a
您必须更新它，所以这是一个
good reason to start the early access
开始抢先体验的充分理由
builds now to be aware of all these
现在建立要注意所有这些
things sooner rather than later rather
事情迟早不宜过
than when you were running to job jt9
比你跑jt9的时间
fuse done rope to help support
熔断完成的绳索以帮助支撑
modularity we'll even breaking binary
模块化，我们甚至将打破二进制
compatibility in a few cases this was
在某些情况下的兼容性
documented at the end of Java SE 8 and
在Java SE 8和
we've implemented in nine there are some
我们已经在九个实施
unfortunate dependencies on Java
对Java的不幸依赖
in far-flung parts of the platform like
在平台的遥远部分
java.util jar which is part of the base
java.util jar是基础的一部分
module so we don't want the base module
模块，所以我们不需要基本模块
to have to depend on beans in terms of
必须依靠豆子
property change listener so we got rid
属性更改侦听器，所以我们摆脱了
of those methods and not so it has a
这些方法中的一个不是
binary incompatible change but we feel
二进制不兼容的更改，但我们感到
the sufficient justification to make it
充分的理由
in nine we're also going to have a more
在九年中，我们还将拥有更多
muscular deprecation policy in nine and
九点和九点的肌肉弃用政策
we'll be hearing more about that later
我们稍后会听到更多
in the talk and that's the help better
在谈话中，这是更好的帮助
manage transitions across JDK is over
管理跨JDK的过渡已结束
the years all right so now we'll start
好多年，所以现在我们开始
talking about tooling improvements first
首先谈论工具改进
one I'll talk about is J shell in
我要谈论的是J shell in
historical perspective a common way of
历史观点是一种常见的方式
implementing with many other language
用许多其他语言实施
environments especially in the lips Lisp
环境，尤其是嘴唇Lisp
tradition has been an interactive shell
传统一直是互动的壳
called a read evaluate print loop or
称为读取评估打印循环或
repple now there's similar functionality
repple现在有类似的功能
you may have seen for other languages
您可能已经看过其他语言
you use like Ruby and Python and on the
您可以使用Ruby和Python等
JDK on the JVM side Scala groovy and so
JVM端的JDK Scala groovy等
forth so what about Java now we have one
等等，那么Java现在有一个
command that does this called a J shell
执行此命令的命令称为J shell
and JDK 9 I'll do a quick teaser demo of
和JDK 9，我将做一个简短的预告片演示
that
那
so Jay shells are command in the jet k9
所以Jay的炮弹是喷气式K9的命令
bin directory so we can just get that
bin目录，这样我们就可以得到
started here on a jet ek build so you
从这里开始就开始了，所以你
have you have a shell a good thing to do
你有壳要做吗
in a shell is get some help so you can
在外壳中可以获得一些帮助，因此您可以
print that out here if the screen was a
如果屏幕是
more usual size the help output would be
通常的大小是帮助输出
more useful and I will make this now the
更有用，我现在将使其
output should fit on the screen not
输出应适合屏幕而不是
quite even when you think you've gotten
即使你以为自己得到了
things set up ahead of time sometimes
有时会提前设置
you have it okay here we go so what's
你还好吧，我们去吧，那是什么
the first program you write in a
您在其中编写的第一个程序
programming language hello world so we
编程语言你好世界，所以我们
can start typing that right here and hit
可以在这里开始输入并点击
return and J shell valuates out his
返回，J Shell评估了他的
expression so notice we didn't have to
表达，所以请注意我们不必
do any public static void main string
做任何公共static void主字符串
you know args all that we can just start
你知道我们可以开始的所有事情
typing right away and get some results
立即输入并获得一些结果
but that's not a terribly compelling we
但这并不是我们的强项
can also define variables in J shells so
也可以在J shell中定义变量，因此
let's say we wanted to find a double
假设我们想找到一个双
variate tau that's equal to two times pi
等于pi的两倍的变量tau
and pi is of course in the math class so
pi当然在数学课上，所以
if we do autocomplete hitting tab J
如果我们执行自动完成，请点击标签J
shell will list the choices here so if
Shell将在此处列出选择，因此如果
we type P for pi that completes for us
我们为pi输入P即可完成
so that's a that's about twice pi so
所以大约是圆周率的两倍
that's good we can find methods in J
很好，我们可以在J中找到方法
shell
贝壳
so let's say we want to define a
假设我们要定义一个
squaring method that takes a X and
取X和的平方方法
returns x times itself so let's add it
返回自身的x倍，因此我们将其添加
to our environment now and now we can
到现在我们的环境
evaluate additional expressions using
使用评估其他表达式
this so let's say we want to square
这么说，我们想平方
autocomplete for that math dot sign you
该数学点符号自动完成
can take that and we can use the
可以接受，我们可以使用
variable we had previously tau we can do
我们以前可以做的变量
usual command line editing and if we
通常的命令行编辑，如果我们
take the sine of a angle and add it the
取一个角度的正弦并添加
square of the sine of an angle and add
角正弦的平方并加
it to the square of the cosine and we
它到余弦的平方，我们
should get something close to one and
应该得到接近一个的东西
that's indeed deed what happens here
那的确是事实
go back to the presentation out so a few
回到演示文稿那么多
things about this if you're a new
如果您是新手，此事
student getting started with Java
学生开始使用Java
there's a lot less ceremony you can just
可以减少很多仪式
start typing your expression right away
立即开始输入您的表情
without having to avoid this well what
而不必避免这种情况
does public static void mean like well
公共静态无效意味着是否也很好
it's a long story we'll get to it later
长话短说，我们稍后再讲
in the course you don't do that anymore
在课程中，您不再这样做
but this is not just a feature for for
但这不仅是针对
students or people learning for Java
学生或学习Java的人们
it's also very helpful for experienced
对经验丰富的人也很有帮助
developers this is a good way to explore
开发人员，这是探索的好方法
using those new 9ap eyes where if you
使用那些新的9ap眼睛，如果您
haven't upgraded to JDK yet you know the
还没有升级到JDK，但是您知道
new API is that you haven't worked with
新的API是您尚未使用的
so far and we found this very useful in
到目前为止，我们发现这在
the jdk group playing with new new
jdk组玩新游戏
language features in terms of how J
语言功能方面如何J
shells implemented it uses a lot of
外壳实现它使用了很多
interesting technologies indicate JDK
有趣的技术表明JDK
including a API to programmatically call
包括用于以编程方式调用的API
Java C and some debugging api's and the
Java C和一些调试api以及
lead engineer for J shell Robert field
J Shell Robert领域的首席工程师
will be giving a more detailed talk
将进行更详细的演讲
about J shell later in the conference
会议稍后将介绍有关J Shell的信息
Javadoc so for many years Java doc has
Javadoc这么多年了，Java doc拥有
been outputting HTML 401 a few years ago
几年前一直输出HTML 401
there is a a new HTML standard html5
有一个新的HTML标准html5
came out and now Java doc can output
出来了，现在Java文档可以输出了
html5 as an opt-in basis even though
html5作为选择加入的基础，即使
it's outputting html5 there are no
它输出html5没有
videos by default though so the Java doc
视频默认情况下，因此Java文档
output still looks basically the same as
输出看起来基本上与
before in terms of a frames style layout
之前的框架样式布局
how many people will have work with
有多少人一起工作
dockland we introduced in JDK 8 there's
我们在JDK 8中引入的Dockland
a few hands there perhaps a few grumbles
几只手，也许几下牢骚
with unwanted warnings or errors in your
带有不必要的警告或错误
build dockland is a lint checker on the
建立码头区是一个皮棉检查器
structure and semantics of your Java doc
Java文档的结构和语义
tags that works both in Java C as well
标记也可以在Java C中使用
as Java doc so you can add it to your
作为Java文档，因此您可以将其添加到
build we've added some additional
建立，我们增加了一些额外的
controls for dock lint in jdk 9 besides
JDK 9中的码头棉绒控件
the previous controls or which
以前的控件或
categories of errors you can now limit
您现在可以限制的错误类别
the doclet checking to particular
doclet检查特定
packages for example in the JDK build we
例如在JDK构建中的软件包
only document the Java X the Java dot X
仅记录Java X Java点X
in Java X dot star packages
在Java X点星程序包中
these are there particular dockland
这些有特别的码头
categories and they do range over from
类别，它们的范围从
the syntax of the HTML to the semantics
HTML的语义语法
of it so you can do things like if you
这样，您就可以像
reference a at sea or at link to a
在海上或在链接上引用一个
method that doesn't there that's a
不存在的方法是
semantic error and that can fail they
语义错误，可能会使它们失败
fail the bill at that point so you can
当时未能通过帐单，因此您可以
make sure to keep it up to date are
确保保持最新
there any doclet writers in the audience
观众中有任何doclet作家
not not this time so the standard doclet
这次不是，所以标准doclet
is the most common doclet that we use to
是我们最常用的doclet
generate the HTML as part of the Javadoc
生成HTML作为Javadoc的一部分
output but you can write your own
输出，但您可以编写自己的
doclets to the original doclet api is
原始doclet api的doclet是
very old I think it's fair to say it
很老了，我认为这很公平
would not it doesn't follow current best
会不会不是目前最好的
practices in Java API design so with the
API设计中的实践
benefit of hindsight we've been able to
后见之明，我们已经能够
design a better API is including a
设计更好的API包括
better language model that's more
更好的语言模型
extensible and we've read the Java doc
可扩展的，我们已经阅读了Java文档
command on top of the new API and not
在新API之上的命令，而不是
another Java doc feature we're excited
我们很兴奋的另一个Java文档功能
about in JDK 9 is search I'll do a quick
在JDK 9中是关于搜索的，我将快速进行
demo of that
演示
all right so now you can see in the
好的，现在您可以在
upper right-hand corner of the Javadoc
Javadoc的右上角
output is a search box and you can start
输出是一个搜索框，您可以开始
typing into it so let's look for math so
输入它，让我们寻找数学
this shows a few things here it finds
这显示了它发现的一些东西
occurrences of math in the package names
软件包名称中出现数学运算
so the Javadoc math package in the base
所以基础中的Javadoc数学包
module as well as type names so Java
模块以及类型名称，因此Java
lying math in Java math big decimal it
躺在Java数学中的数学大十进制吗
also goes down to two methods and fields
也分为两种方法和领域
farther along this also works over
更远的地方也可以解决
modules so if you want to look for the
模块，因此，如果您要查找
base module that can pop up right there
可以在那里弹出的基本模块
and then you can go to the Javadoc page
然后您可以转到Javadoc页面
for the base module you can see the
对于基本模块，您可以看到
packages in that module as well so you
也可以将该模块打包
won't have to use the search engine as
不必将搜索引擎用作
often to find things in java rock you
经常在Java中找到东西让您震惊
can just search right in Java doc
可以直接在Java文档中搜索
instead this is a client-side
相反，这是一个客户端
implementation JavaScript as I mentioned
我提到的实现JavaScript
it does index the names of packages
它确实索引包的名称
types feel fields and methods there's
类型感觉领域和方法
also a way you can add additional index
也可以添加其他索引的方法
terms for your own items if you choose
您自己的商品的条款（如果您选择）
to do so the next two features are going
为此，接下来的两个功能
to be about facilities to help
关于帮助的设施
transition from one JDK to another one
从一个JDK过渡到另一个
in the future both release jar files and
将来都会发布jar文件和
the Java C dash dash release option
Java C破折号发行选项
first up the - - release option for many
首先-许多发行选项
years Java C has been able to cross
Java C已经能够跨越
compile back to older JDK s in the Java
用Java编译回旧的JDK
C man page and elsewhere there's been a
C手册页和其他地方
description of how to do this you have
您如何执行此操作的说明
to do three things you have to set the
做三件事，你必须设置
source to the Roshan you want the target
向您想要的目标Roshan采购
for the class file version you want in
用于您想要的类文件版本
finally you have to set the boot class
最后，您必须设置启动类
path for the RT r r TR classes if of the
RT rr TR类的路径，如果
older lease do those three things we've
较早的租约完成了我们要做的三件事
starting to dedicate restricted the
开始致力于限制
range of old versions we support to one
我们支持的旧版本范围
plus three back
再加三回
so in jdk 9 in particular 9 is the
因此在jdk 9中，特别是9是
default we support 8 and 7 as well as 6
默认情况下，我们支持8和7以及6
but 6 is deprecated and you get a
但不赞成使用6，您会得到一个
warning issued when you use it so
使用时发出警告
likewise when we roll them out into jdk
同样，当我们将它们推出到jdk中时
10 will support
10将支持
10987 when 7 will be deprecated all
10987，届时7将全部弃用
right so why do you have to set the boot
对，那你为什么要设置启动
classpath well let's take an example
类路径很好，让我们举个例子
here in jdk n we have library that has a
在jdk n中，我们有一个具有
food method and then in jdk n plus 1 we
食物方法，然后在jdk n加1中
add an over load foo that takes an int
添加一个int的重载foo
in terms of our compatibility policy
根据我们的兼容性政策
this is a fine change it shouldn't cause
这是一个很好的变化，不应引起
many problems and let's say we have our
很多问题，假设我们有
client library here that has a foo with
这里的客户端库具有foo
an integer argument all right that's
整数参数可以
good so let's say we take this code we
好，让我们说我们采用这段代码
compile it against this JDK but we run
针对这个JDK编译它，但是我们运行
it against this JDK so when we compile
它针对这个JDK，所以当我们编译时
it against JDK n plus 1 the compiler C
针对JDK n加1的编译器C
okay you have a foo method it takes an
好吧，你有一个foo方法需要一个
int so which which foo method is going
int，哪个foo方法要执行
to call in the class file but the one
调用班级文件，但一个
that takes an int or one one six double
需要一个整数或一一六倍的整数
its going to compile down to the one it
它会编译成一个
takes in it that's the more specific one
接受它是更具体的一个
that's what's required by the language
这就是语言所需要的
specification so then when you go to run
规格，然后当您运行时
that class file against the earlier JDK
针对早期JDK的该类文件
even if you set the class file version
即使您设置了类文件版本
appropriately you'll get a message like
适当地，您会收到一条消息，例如
this no such method error and what this
这个没有这样的方法错误，这是什么
basically means is it's looking for a
基本上意味着它正在寻找
fool event and it's not finding it and
愚人事件，没有找到它，
that's correct because there's no food
没错，因为没有食物
in there there's only foo of double so
那里只有双倍的foo
this is why you have to set the boot
这就是为什么您必须设置启动
class path to avoid this sort of
避免这种情况的类路径
situation but people kept running into
情况，但人们不断遇到
this in JIT back in JDK 7 we said you
在JIT 7中的JIT中，我们说过
know people keep owning into this will
知道人们继续拥有这个意志
give a warning if they use the older
如果他们使用较旧的则发出警告
source or target without setting the
源或目标，而无需设置
boot class path so we did that that
引导类路径，所以我们做到了
helped a little bit but we still kept
有所帮助，但我们仍然坚持
having bugs come in
有虫子进来
so in JDK 9 we thought you know what why
所以在JDK 9中，我们认为您知道为什么
don't we just actually provide the
我们不只是提供
feature people art people want to use
特色人物，艺术人物想使用
here which is to cross compile to the
这里是交叉编译到
old version and make that easier to do
旧版本，使它更容易实现
instead so that's just what we did with
相反，这就是我们所做的
the - - release flag a note on that
--释放关于该标记的注释
we're adopting a more the new style
我们正在采用更多新样式
options convention so - - release or
选项约定--发布或
suggest - release so this is
建议-释放，所以这是
semantically equivalent to doing all
语义上等同于全部
three of setting the source the target
设定来源的三个目标
and the blue class path to the old RTR
以及通往旧RTR的蓝色路线
now the information from the old RTR is
现在旧RTR的信息是
the old version of the platform is
该平台的旧版本是
stored as part of Java C it's part
作为Java C的一部分存储，它是
the JDK build now so it's a compressed
现在是JDK构建，因此它是压缩的
format as another benefit as in one way
格式化是另一种好处
to help you're ready for modules that
帮助您准备好要使用的模块
the - - release will only provide the
--版本仅提供
api's for the older versions that you're
api适用于您使用的较旧版本
supposed to use so it'll only provide
应该使用，所以它只会提供
the java SE AAP is that are part of the
Java SE AAP是
standard as well as the exported api is
标准以及导出的api是
in the jdk and it's the same set of
在jdk中，它是相同的
release values as for source and target
释放源和目标值
so this has a few advantages if you were
因此，如果您
being diligent in using the old audio
勤于使用旧音频
jars you don't have to manage that
您无需管理的罐子
anymore you don't have to try to get
不再需要尝试
that from somewhere to address this
从某个地方来解决这个问题
problem people sometimes use maven
问题的人有时会使用Maven
plugins like animal sniffer that's come
像动物嗅探器这样的插件
up some time so you should have less
有一些时间，所以你应该少
need to do that because it's just right
需要这样做，因为它是正确的
in Java C another advantage is is we may
在Java C中，另一个优势是我们可以
make improvements to Java C in newer new
在新版本中对Java C进行改进
releases there are bug fixes sometimes
版本有时会修复错误
we're performance improvements and you
我们正在改善性能，您
can take advantage of them if you use
如果您使用，可以利用它们
the - release flag and we'll see an
-release标志，我们将看到一个
example that later in the talk so multi
这个例子在后来的演讲中如此多
release jar files so if you have a
释放jar文件，以便如果您有
library it's inconvenient to have
图书馆很不方便
different jar files or artifacts for it
不同的jar文件或工件
to correspond to different versions of
对应不同版本的
the JDK you prefer just to have one
您更喜欢拥有一个JDK
artifact and distribute that instead so
工件并分配它，因此
that has a few downstream effects it
有一些下游影响
means there's slower adoption of new
意味着采用新技术的速度较慢
features because more people are
功能，因为更多的人
compiling for the against the original
针对原版进行编译
jar files now you can work around some
jar文件，现在您可以解决一些问题
of these problems occasionally using
这些问题偶尔使用
reflection so like if you want to call a
反思，就像你想打电话给
new innate API only when you're running
仅在运行时才使用新的固有API
on 8 you can check for it reflectively
您可以在8上进行反光检查
and all that so that sometimes works but
而所有这些有时会起作用，但是
it's awkward code and it certainly
这是尴尬的代码，当然
slower runtime than just using a normal
运行时间比仅使用普通模式慢
call now another feature is that with
现在调用的另一个功能是
the modularity support coming in 9 it's
9中的模块化支持
going to be harder to access the api's
很难访问api的
you shouldn't be using like those
你不应该像那样使用
tempting some dot star AP is that many
吸引一些明星AP
people find helpful from now again but
人们从现在起再次找到帮助，但
you've well I got a policy of not
你很好，我有一个不
calling them so you won't be able to get
打电话给他们，这样您将无法获得
to them as easily in 9 so as an
在9中对他们来说就像
alternative we added a multi release jar
或者，我们添加了一个多释放罐
feature in 9 so there's a common area of
9中有一个功能
the jar files as before that shared
和以前共享的jar文件一样
across all the releases then there's
在所有发行版中，
platform-specific overrides put in meta
放置在meta中的特定于平台的替代
inversions so if you have a base draw
倒数，所以如果你有基本平局
file for 8 you can put nine specific
文件8可以放9个具体
class files that kind of override the
覆盖此类的类文件
other class files in a versions nine
版本九中的其他类文件
directory similarly similarly for ten
目录类似地类似十
and so forth you create these with the
依此类推，您可以使用
jar command using some extra options and
jar命令使用一些额外的选项和
the other parts of the platform that
平台的其他部分
read jar files including the draw file
读取jar文件（包括绘图文件）
API in Java util as well as java c do
Java util和Java C中的API
are aware of the multi release jar files
知道多版本的jar文件
now we'll next talk about a number of
现在我们接下来将讨论一些
the language changes made in jdk 9 first
首先在jdk 9中进行语言更改
I'll talk about a set of milling project
我将讨论一组铣削项目
coin features milling on a coin is is
硬币特征是在硬币上铣削是
the name for putting those ridges along
沿着这些山脊排列的名称
the edge that was originally done as an
最初作为
effort to avoid debasing the currency
努力避免使货币贬值
back when coins use made of precious
当硬币使用贵重物品制成时返回
metals people kind of shave down the
金属人有点刮胡子
edges to you know get the silver or gold
你知道的边缘得到银或金
and sell it separately to kind of
并单独出售给某种
devalue the currency so four million
货币贬值，所以四百万
coins was meant to prevent that in our
硬币是为了防止这种情况在我们
sense here million project wine is meant
感觉这里有百万项目葡萄酒
to keep the value of the coin features
保持硬币特征的价值
up to date by fixing some unfinished
通过修复一些未完成的内容
work from early releases these were the
早期版本的工作是
feature set in JDK 7 we were generally
我们通常在JDK 7中设置功能
happy with that at the end of the
对此感到满意
release however there are a few features
发布但是有一些功能
where we wanted to tweak it a little bit
我们想对其进行微调的地方
but we ran out our time in the release
但是我们在发布中用尽了时间
so we're getting back to finish that now
所以我们现在要完成
first one of these o project lambda is
这些lambda项目的第一个是
in a similar situation they also had
在类似情况下，他们也有
some work they didn't manage to get to
他们无法完成的一些工作
at the end of JDK 8 so we're including
在JDK 8的末尾，所以我们包括
that as part of milling project coin in
作为铣削项目硬币的一部分
JDK 9 first up is safe VAR args on
首先使用JDK 9是安全的VAR参数
private instance methods so this is a
私有实例方法，所以这是一个
code you could have written in the JDK
您可能已经在JDK中编写的代码
for many years back from JDK 5 you have
从JDK 5开始已有很多年了
a list of lists of strings and you're
字符串列表的列表
using some platform classes arrays that
使用一些平台类数组
as list to initialize it so it all looks
作为初始化它的列表，所以看起来
fine when you run this through Java C
通过Java C运行时很好
though you'll notice you'll get a
虽然您会注意到您会得到一个
warning like this
这样的警告
uncheck generic array creation for VAR X
取消选中VAR X的通用数组创建
parameter type list of string array so
字符串数组的参数类型列表
it certainly sounds very very
当然听起来非常非常
intimidating that something might be be
恐吓某事
going wrong here this sort of warning is
在这里出现这种警告是错误的
mandated by the
由...授权
it is possible that something bad is
有可能是坏事
happening something called ulti
发生了一些事情
pollution this is discussed in the Java
污染这在Java中讨论
language specification basically there's
语言规范基本上有
a bad interaction between arrays in
数组之间的不良互动
generics that could possibly occur in
可能会出现在
this situation now in this particular
现在在这种情况下
current using arrays that as list
当前使用作为列表的数组
nothing bad actually happens the sort of
实际上没有什么不好的事情发生
bad things that could happen don't
可能发生的坏事不会
happen in this case and that is a nature
在这种情况下发生，这是自然
of doing this kind of a soundness
做这样的健全
analysis so if you have a analysis you
分析，所以如果您有分析
want to be sound that means you have to
想要发出声音，这意味着您必须
warn if you can't know that something
警告如果您不知道某事
bad doesn't happen but that's not
坏事不会发生，但这不是
informative in this case this is
在这种情况下翔实的是
basically a false positive and we wanted
基本上是假阳性，我们想要
to address this situation with project
用项目解决这种情况
Coyne back in seven so what we did we
柯恩（Coyne）回来了七个，所以我们做了什么
added a new annotation type safe VAR
添加了新的注释类型安全VAR
args that basically means trust me I'm
args基本上意味着相信我
not doing anything bad in the VAR args
在VAR参数中没有做任何坏事
method you know the sort of heat
你知道那种热量的方法
pollution problem that's not going to
不会解决的污染问题
occur here and we updated the platform
发生在这里，我们更新了平台
methods as appropriate to have this
适当的方法有这个
annotation that did two things it got
注释完成了两件事
rid of warnings in the declaration of
在声明中摆脱警告
the method but more importantly it got
方法，但更重要的是
rid of warnings at all the uses of these
消除所有这些警告的使用
methods so all the user code that call
方法，因此所有调用的用户代码
these methods didn't have those warnings
这些方法没有这些警告
anymore so that was pretty good
如此，这是相当不错的
due to some aspects of the design of
由于设计的某些方面
annotations you can only apply this
注释，您只能应用此
annotation to methods that cannot be
注释不能的方法
overridden so what are some kinds of
覆盖了，那么有哪些
methods in Java that can't be overridden
Java中无法覆盖的方法
well we can't override final methods by
好吧，我们不能通过以下方法覆盖最终方法
by definition we also can't override
根据定义，我们也不能覆盖
static methods now for the same reason
出于同样的原因，现在使用静态方法
we can't override constructors from a
我们无法从
certain point of view a constructor is
构造函数的某些观点是
this a very special static method that's
这是一个非常特殊的静态方法
kind of how it looks at the VM side so
在虚拟机方面看起来如何
we can't so you use in there now there's
我们不能，所以你现在在那里使用
actually another kind of method we can't
实际上是我们无法做到的另一种方法
override either and that is private
覆盖其中之一，这是私有的
methods now private methods were emitted
现在发出了私有方法
from the list of methods you can use say
从可以使用的方法列表中说
for args on in jdk 7 and now we're
在jdk 7中打开args，现在我们
fixing that in jdk 9 and this is a very
在jdk 9中修复它，这是一个非常
small language change I will show the
小小的语言变化，我将展示
entire specification change on the
整个规格变更
screen now so we like it when we get
现在屏幕，所以我们喜欢它
nice simple to
很简单
just like this because they happen so
就这样，因为它们发生了
rarely so they're usually they're much
很少，所以他们通常是很多
more complicated next up we have some
接下来比较复杂，我们有一些
changes to the tribes resource statement
部落资源声明的变更
to have it use effectively final
使其有效地最终使用
variables just a quick refresher the Tri
变量只是快速入门Tri
of resources statement so you have your
资源声明，以便您拥有
resource being managed and basically the
被管理的资源，基本上
tribes resources make sure you the close
部落资源确保您接近
method gets called when you leave a
当您离开一个
block so it gets roughly translated by
块，以便它大致翻译为
the compiler or something like this so
编译器或类似的东西
there's an additional try finally around
最后还有另外的尝试
around your block here and you make sure
在这里，你确定
to call close it's actually more
呼叫关闭实际上更多
complicated so in terms of full
如此复杂
disclosure this is what Java C actually
公开这实际上是Java C
does on our behalf but you don't we
代表我们做，但你不是我们
don't to worry about this because Java C
不用担心，因为Java C
takes care about that takes care of this
照顾那个
the extra complication is because of
额外的并发症是因为
some nuances of exception handling
异常处理的一些细微差别
so in jdk 7 the resources being managed
因此在jdk 7中正在管理的资源
have to be done under a fresh variable
必须在一个新变量下完成
declared as part of the Tri earth
宣布为三大地球的一部分
resources statement now if you follow
如果您关注，请立即声明资源
project coining JDK 7 that wasn't the
并非JDK 7的项目
original proposal originally you could
最初的建议你可以
have any expression here that have the
在这里有任何表达
type auto closable which was the new
自动关闭类型，这是新的
type created to to host the close method
创建类型以托管close方法
but we figured out that this could be
但是我们发现这可能是
problematic so let's say we have a
有问题，所以我们说我们有一个
resource here we have it point to a
这里的资源指向
first resource resource one we pass that
我们通过的第一个资源
in ok it has the right type and then
好的，它具有正确的类型，然后
within the try block we change our to
在try块中，我们将其更改为
point to a different object resource 2
指向不同的对象资源2
now we exist a try block which object
现在我们存在一个try块，哪个对象
should have its close method call so
应该有其close方法调用，所以
this is a bit of a problem and it in
这是一个问题，它在
particular it's a problem we didn't want
特别是我们不想要的问题
to have to solve so we we decided that
必须解决，所以我们决定
you know what we're just not going to
你知道我们不会去做什么
allow that we're not going to allow the
允许我们不会允许
situation by requiring you to have a
要求您有一个情况
fresh resource variable so we won't have
新鲜的资源变量，所以我们不会
to run into that situation that was a
遇到那种情况
bit overly strict though because there
有点太严格了，因为
are variables that can't be modified in
是无法在其中修改的变量
a tri or three sources block like final
三或三个来源像最终
variables or effectively final variables
变量或有效的最终变量
which are variables that the program
这些是程序的变量
would compile if you made them final but
如果您将它们定为最终版本，则会进行编译，
you just haven't made them final yet so
你只是还没有让他们决赛而已
what we can do now is to take advantage
我们现在能做的就是利用
of that if you have a variable that's
如果你有一个变量
final or effectively final
最终或有效地最终
instead of declaring a new variable in
而不是在中声明新变量
the try of resources statement to host
尝试资源声明托管
it you can just pass it in directly and
您可以直接将其传递给
since you can't to change are inside the
因为你不能改变是在里面
block we don't have the problem of like
块，我们没有像
which object to call it's closed method
哪个对象调用它的封闭方法
on here's the grammar changes for that
在这方面的语法变化
not not very hard to the grammar change
语法变化不是很困难
the spec change is bigger as we expect
规格变化比我们预期的更大
here it's a little more complicated than
在这里，它比
you might suspect so you might think
你可能会怀疑，所以你可能会想
like well you just need to have like
就像你只需要拥有
final local variables or something
最终局部变量之类的
we prefer if the language changes or
如果语言发生变化，我们希望
more orthogonal so you can actually do
更加正交，因此您实际上可以
things like if you have a final field
如果你有最后的领域
within a newly allocated object
在新分配的对象中
well that's final - so you can use that
好吧，这是最终的-所以您可以使用它
in your try earth resources statement
在您尝试地球资源的声明中
instead and that's what the longer
相反，那是更长的时间
specification here allows you to do next
此处的规格允许您下一步
language change has to deal with diamond
语言变化必须应对钻石
diamonds are made under the earth and
钻石是在地下制造的，
great heat and pressure and will have to
巨大的热量和压力，将不得不
go down the rabbit hole a little bit to
往兔子洞下一点
see why this feature is needed but it is
看看为什么需要此功能，但这是
a good change we have the got into nine
一个好的变化，我们有九个
so we using this little example of a box
所以我们用这个盒子的小例子
type you can think of a box as a
类型，您可以将盒子视为
simplified collection justified you take
简化的收藏证明你采取
objects it you put objects in and get
您放入对象并获得的对象
objects out so you have a list of
对象出来，所以你有一个清单
question mark here and you want a new
问号在这里，你想要一个新的
box to hold the the list so this should
框来保存列表，所以这应该
be fine so what happens with this
很好，这会发生什么
diamond so inside the compiler the
菱形，所以在编译器中
compiler needs to infer a type to use
编译器需要推断要使用的类型
for box so Java is still a statically
for box，所以Java仍然是静态的
typed language it's just not always a
打字的语言并不总是
explicitly typed language meaning the
显式输入语言，表示
compiler sometimes infers the types on
编译器有时会推断类型
our behalf as programmers so what does
我们代表程序员，所以做什么
that look like inside Java C so the type
在Java C中看起来像这样
disk inferred is list of capture of
推断的磁盘是捕获的列表
question mark so you can't write a type
问号，所以你不能写一个类型
list of capture fresh mark in your
您的捕获新鲜标记列表
source code so what's going on here well
源代码，所以这里的情况很好
this is something called capture
这就是所谓的捕获
conversion and this is a non de notable
转换，这不是很明显
type which is described in the JLS now
现在在JLS中描述的类型
this is a part of the JLS where you
这是JLS的一部分
might want to have a type theory book
可能想要一本类型理论书
nearby to help figure out what's going
在附近以帮助弄清楚发生了什么
on basically what's
基本上是什么
means that is often the case in
就是说
languages there's a richer type system
语言有更丰富的类型系统
inside the compiler than the one made
在编译器内部比一个
available to the programmer
可供程序员使用
so when Java C sees a wild card the
因此，当Java C看到通配符时，
question mark type here it translates
问号类型在这里翻译
that down to a new fresh type variable
直到一个新的新鲜类型变量
inside the compiler and reasons about it
编译器内部及其原因
that's what the CAPTCHA conversion
这就是验证码转换
process entails so you have your box
过程需要，所以你有你的盒子
class one thing you can do with the box
你可以用盒子做一件事
you can subclass it it has public
你可以把它公开化
constructors and you can also subclass
构造函数，您也可以子类化
it anonymously all right so that might
匿名可以，这样可能
be okay but maybe it's not so how do you
可以，但也许不是，那你怎么办
how do you compile down an anonymous
你如何编译一个匿名者
subclass so there's a full class file
子类，所以有完整的类文件
for it so if we would write in a source
为此，如果我们要在源代码中编写
code look something like class of box
代码看起来像盒子类
dollar one extends the box and we need
一美元可以扩展包装盒，我们需要
to have some type to fill in for what
有某种类型填写什么
how it extends box and the type that's
它如何扩展框和类型
in furbot compiler is this list of
在Furbot编译器中，此列表是
captures question mark so far so good
到目前为止很好地捕获了问号
however there's a bit of a problem here
但是这里有一个问题
because this information has to be
因为此信息必须是
stored in the signature attribute of a
存储在
class file the grammar of the signature
类文件签名的语法
attribute does not allow nonde notable
属性不允许非显着
types like list of capture question mark
诸如捕获问号列表之类的类型
to be stored to be represented so this
要存储以表示
is a this is a problem here of using
是一个使用这里的问题
Dimond with anonymous classes when you
当您拥有匿名类的Dimond
have these non inaudible types so what's
有这些不可听见的类型，那是什么
been the interaction here over time way
随着时间的推移一直在这里互动
way back in 1.1 many years ago inner
早在1.1年前的内在
classes were added years later generics
几年后增加了类
were added the generics were added in a
加入了泛型
way that interacted with inner classes
与内部类交互的方式
so that was fine then in JDK 7 we had a
这样很好，然后在JDK 7中
diamond and inner classes in diamond
钻石和钻石内部阶层
interacting together work fine inner
互动在一起很好的内在
classes engineer diamond in generics
通用类工程师钻石
interacting together separately work
单独互动在一起工作
fine but when we combine all through
很好，但是当我们结合在一起
these three things together we get a
这三件事在一起，我们得到了
visit from Fang this is Duke's evil twin
来自方舟子的来访这是杜克大学的邪恶双胞胎
brother who's coming to mess up our
来搞砸我们的兄弟
plans to improve the language and as a
计划改善语言，并作为
brian gets this fond of say this is a
布赖恩喜欢这样说
case where yet today's problems come
今天还存在问题的情况
from yesterday's solutions where these
从昨天的解决方案中，这些
language features made
语言功能
or decade apart had this very
或相隔十年
unfortunate interaction this was
不幸的互动，这是
actually discovered by our jck team and
实际上是由我们的jck团队发现的，
they're writing performance tests for
他们正在为编写性能测试
the feature back in seven
七分之内的功能
so unfortunately seven the solution had
不幸的是有七个解决方案
like you know what this sounds kind of
就像你知道这听起来像什么
complicated to deal with we're just not
处理起来很复杂，我们不是
going to let you use Dimond with
让你用Dimond与
anonymous classes so that will avoid
匿名类，这样可以避免
this problem for sure that was a little
这个问题肯定是一点
unfortunate so when we were finishing up
不幸的是，当我们完成时
the JCR 334 specification we did note
我们注意到的JCR 334规范
that you know his future in the platform
你知道他在平台上的未来
we could allow diamond with anonymous
我们可以允许匿名的钻石
subclasses if we don't get those nonde
如果我们不了解这些子类
notable types if we just had a normal
值得注意的类型，如果我们只是正常的
notable type then it'd be fine and we
值得注意的类型，那会很好，我们
could use it and that is in fact what
可以使用它，这实际上是什么
we've done now in JDK not the
我们现在已经在JDK中完成了
specification to do that is is more
规范做到这一点是更多
involved this is how you say non notable
这就是你怎么说不值得注意的
in JLS ease fortunately our spec guys
在JLS中，幸运的是我们的规范人员
take care of that for us so that's here
照顾好我们，就在这里
so what's been the effectiveness of this
那这个的功效是什么
when we were initially designing Dimond
当我们最初设计Dimond时
we could get rid of about 90% of the
我们可以摆脱约90％的
explicit constructor arguments using the
使用的显式构造函数参数
diamond feature in seven and we feel
七个钻石特征，我们感到
that by allowing diamond with de notable
通过允许钻石与
types in anonymous classes we can get
我们可以得到的匿名类中的类型
rid of a lot of the remaining 10% we've
摆脱了我们剩下的很多10％
had good experiences using this feature
在使用此功能方面有很好的经验
in the JDK we've updated hundreds of
在JDK中，我们更新了数百个
call sites to use this often for the
致电网站以经常将其用于
security pillars action next up
安全支柱行动下一步
underscore is no longer an identifier
下划线不再是标识符
name so this is something that's been
名称，所以这已经是
discussed is a part of project lambda a
讨论的是lambda项目的一部分
number of years ago when you have a
几年前，当你有一个
lambda parameter in eight you cannot use
lambda参数中有八种您无法使用
lambda as a parameter name and if you
lambda作为参数名称，如果
use lambda as a parameter name in 8 you
在8中使用lambda作为参数名称
did get a warning from Java C notifying
确实从Java C收到警告，通知
you that well one day you might not be
那一天你可能不会
able to use this as an identifier
能够使用它作为标识符
anymore and indeed that day has has come
确实，那天已经到了
to pass so why are we doing this this is
通过，所以我们为什么要这样做
against our usual policy of keeping
违反了我们一贯的保留政策
programs that compile compiling we feel
我们觉得编译的程序
it's not used very option and if there's
它不是非常有用的选项，如果有
a better future use of it if we reclaim
如果我们回收它，将来会更好地使用它
the syntactic real-estate some things
句法不动产
that might show up our partial diamond
可能会显示我们的部分钻石
so just in for one one type variable
所以只是在一种类型的变量
manage another
管理另一个
or partial writtens like this on generic
或类似的部分书面文章
haul maybe we can encode this is
也许我们可以编码为
something else like parameter names
其他类似参数名称
expressed far not use messages and so
表达远不使用消息等
forth private interface methods one of
第四种私有接口方法之一
the other changes made by lambda in 8
lambda在8中所做的其他更改
was default methods these are methods on
是默认方法，这些是方法
interfaces that have code so they're non
具有代码的接口，因此它们不是
abstract and so these are very helpful
抽象，所以这些非常有帮助
in evolving the platform at the VM level
在虚拟机级别发展平台
it was convenient and necessary to
这是方便和必要的
actually have private methods on
实际上有私有方法
interfaces to help have some of the meta
界面以帮助拥有一些元
Factory stuff go on however at the
工厂的东西继续在
source level you couldn't have private
您无法拥有的源代码级别
methods inside interfaces and now we're
接口内部的方法，现在我们
changing out in 8 so you can also have
换成8，这样您也可以
your own private methods in the source
源代码中您自己的私有方法
code of interfaces you can both have
你们两个都有的接口代码
private static methods in private
私有中的私有静态方法
instance methods so what would you do
实例方法，那么你会怎么做
with such a private method typically you
用这样的私有方法通常
have that as a helper method for the
将其作为辅助方法
default methods in your class so you can
类中的默认方法，因此您可以
put some common code together as a
将一些通用代码放在一起
private interface without exposing that
私有接口而不暴露
to all the users of the interface next
给下一个界面的所有用户
up we'll start talking about about
我们将开始谈论
deprecation and import statements so
弃用和导入语句，因此
it's a bit of background the JDK is
JDK有点背景
large Java code base we've had our share
大型Java代码库
of technical debt over the years this is
多年来的技术债务
a multicolored diagram of the java c
Java C的五彩图
warnings we've had building the jdk
警告我们已经建立了JDK
itself as you can see back in jdk it was
您可以在jdk中看到它本身是
over 10,000 so we had a few number
超过10,000，所以我们有几个
messages in the code base over the years
多年来代码库中的消息
we made progress on this we have some
我们在这方面取得了进展，我们有一些
good interns and some other days and
好实习生和其他日子
later on we started turning warnings on
后来我们开始打开警告
in the bill and from the time of this
从法案开始到现在
diagram stops to you know then later in
图表就停止了，然后在后面
jdk 9 we went from thousands of method
jdk 9我们从成千上万的方法
of warning messages left down to zero so
的警告消息数量降至零，因此
in the core part of the platform the
在平台的核心部分
open code the close code generator code
打开代码关闭代码生成器代码
it's all warning free we build with
我们建立的所有警告都是免费的
excellent W error this covers many of
出色的W错误，涵盖了许多
the dockland features as well so this
码头区也有特色
covers of the core parts of the platform
平台核心部分的封面
meaning the base module and the Java
表示基本模块和Java
based module and desktop module
基于模块和桌面模块
well it does not include things like
好吧，它不包括类似
CORBA jack speed jack ws instead maybe
也许是CORBA插孔速度插孔WS
we'll get to those someday maybe we
我们有一天可能会到
won't
惯于
and people often talk about technical
人们经常谈论技术
debt but I think the benefits of a
债务，但我认为
project like this can be seen as
这样的项目可以看作是
technical dividends there are now entire
现在有技术红利
classes of problems in the JDK we don't
我们没有的JDK中的问题类别
have to worry about anymore because
不必再担心了，因为
they'll be caught by the build and
他们会被建筑和
people fix them right away so for your
人们马上修复它们，以便您
serializable class did you declare a
您是否声明了一个可序列化的类
serial version UID even an exception
串行版本UID甚至是一个例外
type because all exception types of
类型，因为所有的异常类型
realisable how about equals and hashcode
可实现的等于和哈希码
it's easy to make a mistake there
在那里容易犯错
there's a very nuance check we do now in
我们现在进行了非常细微的检查
the compiler that you know make sure you
您知道的编译器确保您
do things properly
做好事
there's even possible security
甚至有可能的安全性
implications something like a switch
暗示像开关
fall through you can execute unexpected
失败可以执行意外
code and that's the same basic problem
代码，这是相同的基本问题
that was in that go to fail go to fail a
那就是去失败去失败一个
security issue from a few years ago and
几年前的安全问题
finally is it really acceptable to have
最后，真的可以接受
more deprecation warnings on a
关于的更多弃用警告
deprecated item so the the very button
不推荐使用的项目，因此按钮
there's I did write a blog entry if you
我确实写了一个博客条目，如果你
want to from the JDK experience removing
想要从JDK体验中删除
warnings recommendations you might want
您可能需要的警告建议
to have for your own project to go
有自己的项目去
through a similar effort now the very
通过类似的努力，现在
bottom layer of that graph of the
该图的最底层
warnings there was a crust of very
警告有一个非常
stubborn deprecation warnings that we
我们顽固的弃用警告
had to get rid of as well deprecation
必须摆脱淘汰
warnings are generated by the use of
警告是通过使用
deprecated types methods and so forth
不推荐使用的类型方法等
these are mandated by the JLS now
这些是JLS现在授权的
there's a few ways you can resolve these
有几种方法可以解决这些问题
warnings you can remove the use of the
警告，您可以删除对
deprecated elements that's great when
不推荐使用的元素，当
you can do it you can't do it all the
你可以做到，你不可能全部做到
time it might be part of the API you can
时间可能是您可以使用的API的一部分
propagate the deprecated annotation to
将不推荐使用的注释传播到
the youth site in this case kind of the
在这种情况下，青年网站
cure is worse than the disease you're
治愈比你患的病还糟
making the deprecated part of the
使过时的部分成为
platform bigger instead of smaller and
平台更大而不是更小
finally you can use the suppress
最后你可以使用抑制
warnings feature to suppress warnings of
警告功能可禁止发出警告
that case and that's what we we often
那是我们经常遇到的情况
did all right so here is a here some
没事吧，这是这里的一些
client code and here's a deprecated
客户代码，这是已弃用的
library so when you run the compiler you
库，因此当您运行编译器时，
see that indeed you do get a warning
看到确实确实收到警告
that it uses deprecated API uses
它使用不推荐使用的API
that blue right here so you say all
那蓝色在这里，所以你说全部
right no problem I can't remove use of
没问题，我不能删除使用
the API I don't want to make my client
我不想让我的客户使用的API
too deprecated so I'll suppress the
太过时了，所以我会抑制
warning instead so right at the top of
而是在顶部警告
the class I'll suppress the warning I'll
上课时我会压制警告
run the compiler again and you still
再次运行编译器，您仍然
have deprecated API warnings so what's
已弃用API警告，那是什么
going on here if you look at more
如果你看更多的话
information Java C is warning you that
信息Java C警告您
well yeah you're using the deputy type
是的，您使用的是代理类型
in the import statement you're not using
在您未使用的导入语句中
the code it's in the import statement
导入语句中的代码
this is also mandated by the JLS you
JLS也要求您这样做
might say well okay I'll just add
可能会说好吧，我将添加
suppress warnings on the import
禁止导入警告
statement that doesn't work
无效的陈述
that's not syntactically allowed so if
这在语法上是不允许的，所以如果
you really wanted to get rid of the
你真的想摆脱
deprecation one you could do something
弃用一个你可以做的事
like for each use of the deprecated type
就像对不推荐使用的类型的每次使用一样
name replace it with a fully qualified
名称以完全合格的名称替换
name of the type instead of the
类型的名称，而不是
important aim well that's a little silly
重要的目标很好，这有点愚蠢
right in the you know the program is
就在您知道程序是
just as bad if it's using a short name
如果使用短名称也一样糟糕
versus the long name so why why do you
相对于长名，为什么呢？
have to go through this fuss instead so
不得不经历这种大惊小怪，所以
we change Java C to not require emitting
我们将Java C更改为不需要发出
a deprecation warning in this location
此位置的弃用警告
so if you're on an import statement you
因此，如果您使用进口声明，
don't have to get the warning and that
不必得到警告，
was an easy fix here just one sentence
很容易解决，这里只有一句话
in the JLS but because of this fix is
在JLS中，但由于此修复程序
now tractable to remove the deprecation
现在易于处理，以消除折旧
warnings from a significant codebase and
来自重要代码库的警告，以及
we have an existence proof of that in
我们有一个存在的证据
the JDK so I encourage you to try to get
JDK，所以我鼓励您尝试获取
rid of the deprecation warnings in your
摆脱您的弃用警告
own code because of this fix there's
自己的代码，因为此修复程序有
actually much more to say about
实际上还有更多要说的
deprecation in jdk 9 that's just part of
jdk 9中的弃用只是一部分
it so what is deprecation mean it's been
所以什么是贬值意味着
a little unclear over the years does it
这些年来有点不清楚
mean that this API is harmful does it
表示此API有害吗
mean it's going away if it means it's
意思是说它要消失了
going away why haven't those guys in the
走开，为什么那些家伙没有
JK group removed any of these things
JK Group删除了这些东西
that have been deprecated for years so
已经被淘汰多年了
we wanted to enhance deprecation aid to
我们想加强对
help answer these questions and make the
帮助回答这些问题并使
management of deprecated API s easier
不推荐使用的API的管理更加轻松
over the years so there's some new
这些年来，有一些新的
methods that were added to the
添加到
annotation one that says whether or not
说明是否
this deprecated item is for removal or
此不推荐使用的项目是为了移除或
not and that defaults to false another
不，默认为另一个
one is since when has the item
一是因为什么时候有项目
deprecated we've updated the deprecated
已弃用，我们已经更新了已弃用
annotations in the core part of the
注释的核心部分
platform to have this additional
这个额外的平台
information in them they're supporting
他们正在支持的信息
updates both in Java language
都以Java语言更新
specification java c and java talk
规范java c和java talk
there's also a new static analysis
还有一个新的静态分析
analysis tool called j deeper scan that
分析工具，称为j更深层扫描
will analyze your class files and draw
将分析您的课程文件并绘制
files for use of ABAP eyes that are
使用ABAP眼睛的文件
deprecated in the JDK so one issue when
在JDK中已弃用，因此当
we add new deprecations to the jdk
我们向jdk添加新的弃用
saying jdk 9 people don't always
说jdk 9人并不总是
recompile their sources so they don't
重新编译他们的资源，这样他们就不会
have a way to get notified that things
有办法得到通知
have been deprecated now so j depper
现在已弃用，因此j depper
scan is meant to resolve that problem
扫描旨在解决该问题
because you can make an existing draw
因为你可以做一个现有的画
file run j deeper scan and see if it's
文件运行j更深层扫描，看是否
using api's that are now deprecated in
使用现在不推荐使用的api
the new version of the JDK there's much
JDK的新版本有很多
more to say about a duplication feature
关于复制功能的更多说明
you can get the full prognosis and
您可以获得完整的预后
history from Stewart marks aka dr.
斯图尔特的历史标志着博士。
deprecated ur at a talk later in the
在稍后的演讲中，您不赞成使用
conference finally we'll talk about some
会议最后我们将讨论一些
mostly library updates besides having a
除了具有
new version with JDK 9 we have a new
JDK 9的新版本，我们有了一个新
version string scheme the summary is
版本字符串方案的摘要是
we're getting rid of the 1 dot in 1.9 so
我们摆脱了1.9中的1点
if we're never going to change the one
如果我们永远不会改变一个
we figured might as well just get rid of
我们认为不妨摆脱
it this is also done to align better
这样做也是为了更好地对齐
with the semantic versioning and things
与语义版本控制和事物
along those lines
沿着这些路线
so this is what the current version
所以这是当前版本
output looks like from JDK 8 build and
输出看起来像来自JDK 8 build和
this is what it looks like now a 9 so if
这就是现在的样子9所以
you have some system that parses the
您有一些系统可以解析
version string output you'll have to
版本字符串输出，您必须
update that a bit if you use native
如果您使用本地更新一点
processes on systems there's a better
系统上的流程有更好的
API to do that now and particularly you
现在就这样做的API，尤其是您
can now get the something represents the
现在可以得到代表的东西
kid of the native process so that's as
本机过程的孩子，所以
handy when you need to do that strings
当您需要做弦时很方便
are one of the most commonly used types
是最常用的类型之一
in in Java there have been some changes
在Java中进行了一些更改
there
那里
the compact string project previously
以前的紧凑字符串项目
inside the string the information was
字符串中的信息是
stored in a car array so that's 16 bits
存储在汽车阵列中，所以16位
per character often is the case that all
每个字符通常都是这样
the characters in the string have the
字符串中的字符具有
upper 8 bit 0 because the characters are
高8位0，因为字符是
all in the the first 128 characters so
全部在前128个字符中，因此
with compact strings now based on the
现在基于紧凑的字符串
contents of this string it always uses a
此字符串的内容始终使用
byte array and sometimes it uses a one
字节数组，有时它使用一个
byte for character encoding and
字节，用于字符编码和
sometimes it uses a 2-byte for character
有时它使用2个字节的字符
encoding so this is transparent to users
编码，因此对用户透明
it's the same API but there's better
它是相同的API，但有更好的
memory density related to strings was
与字符串相关的内存密度为
improving a string concatenation
改善字符串连接
drinking cat nation is another very
喝猫的民族是另一个非常
common operation Java C will generate
Java C将生成的常见操作
calls down to string builder to do this
调用字符串生成器执行此操作
now the pattern of string builder calls
现在，字符串构建器调用的模式
Java C generates and the patterns of
Java C生成和模式
string builder calls a particular VM
字符串生成器调用特定的VM
recognizes as being amiable optimization
认为是和可亲的优化
may differ and they may differ over time
可能会有所不同，并且随着时间的推移可能会有所不同
is one of the other changes so instead
是其他变化之一，所以
to address this because it's the common
解决这个问题，因为这很常见
operation we created a new entry point
操作我们创建了一个新的入口点
in Java line string concatenation and
在Java行字符串连接和
then the VM can recognize especially at
然后VM可以识别
runtime to optimize so again this is
运行时进行优化，所以这再次是
mostly transparent to use it but should
使用它几乎是透明的，但应该
result in better performance for string
为字符串带来更好的性能
builder and it should be future proof in
建造者，它应该是未来的证明
terms of API updates in the future so
将来API更新的条款
it's less brittle in terms of the alphas
就alpha而言，它不那么脆弱
ation front there are other cases where
在其他情况下
improve the engineering of existing
改善现有工程
features one of those is called tiered
功能之一被称为分层
attribution which dealt with type
处理类型的归因
inference in Java C so we've talked
Java C的推论，所以我们谈到了
about type inference before with diamond
关于使用钻石之前的类型推断
so we have it here we have a class with
所以我们在这里有一个课程
generic class we want to have a
我们想要一个通用类
constructor for it you use diamond so
您使用Diamond的构造函数，因此
that's fine so we start compiling it and
很好，所以我们开始编译它，
we start having some nesting of these
我们开始有一些嵌套
constructors it takes a little bit to
构造函数需要一点时间
compile and it's taking longer to get
编译它需要更长的时间
more nesting and hmm it's seeming to
似乎有更多的嵌套和嗯
take a lot longer than it really should
比实际需要的时间更长
for this length of program so if you
对于此程序长度，如果
just have 16 nested calls here on the
在这里只有16个嵌套调用
machine we use this took 25 minutes to
我们用这台机器花了25分钟
compile now it is a bit longer but this
现在编译要长一点，但这
seems kind of excessive and the same
似乎有点过分且相同
thing holds true for lambda if you have
如果有的话，这对lambda成立
nested lambdas like this you can also
这样嵌套的lambda也可以
get very long compile times now now we
现在获得非常长的编译时间
don't want to give people an excuse for
不想给别人找借口
having swordfights waiting for their
等待他们的剑术
class to compile so we can graph this
类进行编译，因此我们可以用图形表示
here the linear scale looks pretty bad
这里的线性比例看起来很糟糕
but we can look at a log scale and you
但我们可以看看对数刻度
were
是
all that if you have a straight line on
如果你有一条直线
a log scale that means you have an
对数刻度表示您有一个
exponential growth curve so this this
指数增长曲线
looks this looks pretty straight here so
看起来在这里看起来很直
this is this is this is not good
这是这个不好
generally in a compiler like Java C you
通常在像Java C这样的编译器中
want to use linear algorithms with
想要使用线性算法
linear growth in the program size or
程序规模的线性增长或
length is linear you can get so
长度是线性的，你可以得到
exponential is pretty far from that
指数远非如此
so we've addressed this in jdk 9 with
所以我们已经在jdk 9中解决了
Trude attribution and so these lines at
原始归属，因此这些行
the bottom show that this is JDK nine
底部显示这是JDK九
plane and this is JDK nine using dash
平面，这是JDK的九个破折号
dash release eight so this means if you
破折号释放八，所以这意味着如果您
compile your eight source code on nine
在9个编译8个源代码
compiler you will avoid this exponential
编译器，您将避免这种指数
slow down here so how is this
在这里慢下来，这怎么样
accomplished type infringe isn't magic
成功的类型侵权不是魔术
or mind-reading it's a form of
或读心术是一种形式
constraint programming so you generate
约束编程，因此您可以生成
lots of constraints and what in the most
很多约束，什么是最
straightforward way to generate
生成的直接方法
constraints generates a lot of them an
约束产生了很多
exponential number of them and then you
他们的指数数目，然后你
solve it so the essence of pure dot
解决它，使纯点的本质
rebuke many ocean which is a fancy way
斥责许多海洋，这是一种奇特的方式
of saying caching so basically when the
基本上说缓存的时候
constraint set was built it didn't add
约束集已建立，未添加
redundant constraints going on and that
多余的约束在继续，那
allows this much faster a solution time
这样可以更快地解决问题
for the type inference so that's good
用于类型推断，所以很好
there there's also lays the groundwork
那里也奠定了基础
for more optimizations for inference in
在推理中进行更多优化
the future there are other parts of the
未来还有其他部分
platform including security libraries
包括安全库的平台
let's see how we're doing on time the
让我们看看我们如何按时
different parts of the security
安全的不同部分
libraries there's Java security itself
库本身具有Java安全性
there's ap is that you can add use with
ap是您可以添加使用
your own codes like photography
您自己的代码（例如摄影）
including SSL for networking there's
包括用于网络的SSL
also a few command-line options like a
还有一些命令行选项，例如
key tool and so forth the policy
关键工具等等政策
security is secure by default that means
默认情况下，安全性是安全的，这意味着
out of the box you can have a secure
开箱即用，您可以拥有一个安全的
configuration even if you have to
配置，即使您必须
reconfigure it differently to be less
重新配置它以减少
secure to meet your own needs and
确保满足您自己的需求，并且
there's a notion this is something
有一个想法，这是东西
that's always changing to keep up to
一直在变化以跟上
date on the security best practice and
关于安全最佳实践的日期，以及
so forth in terms of the algorithms that
就算法而言，
are used Oracle's recently published a
都是Oracle最近发布的
cryptography roadmap this documents when
密码学路线图
in which algorithms aren't going to get
在哪些算法将无法获得
retired so you can make preparations for
退休了，所以你可以为
Kove so in jdk 9 the crypto roadmap and
Kove在jdk 9中如此加密路线图和
secure by default is that a few
默认情况下安全的是
implications we've increased the default
暗示我们增加了默认值
key size in some cases for certificates
在某些情况下证书的密钥大小
weak keys are no longer accepted by
弱键不再被
default so if you have a certificate
默认，所以如果您有证书
using md5 or RSA with short keys those
使用md5或RSA与短键那些
are not going to be accepted anymore and
不再被接受了
the reason is even though the
原因是即使
functionality of you know things like
您的功能知道诸如
RSA and md5 are the same cryptographers
RSA和md5是相同的密码学家
are very clever and they come up with
非常聪明，他们想出了
better ways of attacking the old
更好的攻击旧方法
algorithms and of course compute there's
算法，当然还有计算
more computing resources over time so it
随着时间的推移会有更多的计算资源
was considered secure in the past isn't
过去被认为是安全的
necessarily security more and the way to
必不可少的安全性以及通往
guard against that is to do things like
谨防做这样的事情
use large key sizes and in terms of
使用较大的密钥，并且
preserving behavioral compatibility if
如果保持行为兼容性
you really need to use the older
您真的需要使用较旧的
algorithm for some reason there's
由于某种原因的算法
usually a system property that lets you
通常是一个系统属性，可以让您
do that we've also kept security
这样做我们还保持了安全性
libraries up to date with other
与其他图书馆最新
involvements there's new hash algorithms
涉及新的哈希算法
there's a new random number generator
有一个新的随机数发生器
which they call a deterministic random
他们称之为确定性随机
bit generator instead on the performance
位发生器代替性能
front processors including spark
包括星火的前端处理器
processors and x64 processors will have
处理器和x64处理器将具有
special-purpose instructions have speed
专用指令有速度
up cryptography operations and we take
加密操作，我们采取
advantage of those in JDK nines using
JDK nines使用的优点
something called a hotspot intrinsic so
所谓的热点内在因素
basically hotspot can recognize certain
基本上热点可以识别某些
operations is special and replace them
操作很特殊，请更换
with the corresponding assembly code so
与相应的汇编代码一样
they go nice and fast if you're
如果您愿意，他们会很快又好
interested in security there's a session
对安全性感兴趣的有一个会议
on that it actually happening right now
关于它，实际上现在正在发生
so you can't can't see it but you can
所以你看不到但你可以
probably catch the replay and if not the
可能赶上重播，如果没有
security team is having a ball tomorrow
保安队明天要打球
evening you can catch them there saying
晚上你可以赶上他们说
a few words on the client libraries and
在客户端库上说几句话
JavaFX JavaFX has also been updated for
JavaFX JavaFX也已针对
the modularity features coming in
即将出现的模块化功能
platform as well as high DPI screens for
平台以及高DPI屏幕
the client libraries the genera fication
客户图书馆属
of the client libraries has been
客户端库的
completed this was part of the warnings
完成这是警告的一部分
cleanup effort again we have high DPI
再次清理工作，我们的DPI很高
across operating systems the font layout
跨操作系统的字体布局
has been updated there are a few places
已经更新了一些地方
in the JDK where open JDK in
在JDK中，在其中打开JDK
the Oracle JDK used different code bases
Oracle JDK使用了不同的代码库
one of those was in the graphics
其中之一是在图形中
rendering one use Pisces one use ductus
渲染双鱼座一用导管
and JDK nine they've both been changed
和JDK 9他们都被改变了
to use the new Marlin graphics renderer
使用新的Marlin图形渲染器
if you like TIFF files you can now have
如果您喜欢TIFF文件，现在可以拥有
support for those in the fathom or as
支持那些the昧或
well if you're interested out client
好吧，如果您对客户感兴趣
there's again there's a session right
再次有一个会议权
now that you could have gone to instead
现在你本可以去
but there is a Baath to meet that that
但有一场复兴可以满足
team later in the conference as well a
团队稍后在会议上以及
few miscellaneous small library changes
少量其他小的库更改
that are helpful
有帮助
here's one for convenience factory
这是一家便利工厂
methods so how often have you written a
方法，所以您多久写一次
code like this you want to have a set of
您想要一组这样的代码
strings so you have a hash set and then
字符串，所以您有一个哈希集，然后
like I got initialize it and now you
就像我初始化它，现在你
want to make it on modifiable so I have
想要使其可修改，所以我有
to have this other calls like that's a
像这样有其他电话
bit of a hassle it's a lot of code for
有点麻烦，很多代码
what should be a simple operation this
这应该是一个简单的操作
might say well I'll do something else
可能会说我会做其他事情
instead I'll use a raised dot as list I
相反，我将使用凸起的点作为列表
don't have to have all these add calls
不必所有这些添加呼叫
and ice off to have this wrapper here
和冰去这里有这个包装
there's other ways people get around
人们还有其他出行方式
this I won't even show the trick with
这我什至不展示技巧
the double braces we use anonymous
我们使用匿名的双括号
subclass I know people use it so we
子类，我知道人们会用它，所以我们
don't we don't have to do that anymore
不，我们不必再这样做了
in JDK 9 we can just use code like this
在JDK 9中，我们只能使用这样的代码
ah this is not nice and short yes yes
啊，这不好，简短，是的，是的
thank you yes this is a Stewart Marc's
谢谢，是斯图尔特·马克的
work what's going on here there's new
工作这是怎么回事
static factory methods named of on list
列表上名为的静态工厂方法
set and map they return unmodifiable
设置并映射它们返回的值不可修改
collections to make sure people don't
收藏以确保人们不会
depend on the iteration order we
取决于我们的迭代顺序
randomized it for sets and maps not for
随机将其用于集合和地图，而不用于
lists and if you want to hear more about
列表，如果您想了解更多有关
this the stewart marks who added this
这是斯图尔特标记谁添加了这个
feature is giving a session on
功能正在召开会议
collections later in the conference Java
会议Java的后续集合
util objects has some utilities for
util对象具有一些实用程序
common programming tasks there's some
常见的编程任务有一些
more null handling there's a few methods
更多的null处理有一些方法
to take the TD matter of writing index
拿TD写作问题指数
checks few odds and ends on the
检查几率和结束
mathematical front we have support for a
数学前沿我们支持
fuse multiply add operation which is
保险丝乘加运算是
also going to have intrinsic supports on
也将有内在的支持
a different processor soon if you like
如果您愿意，可以尽快使用其他处理器
taking square roots you can now not only
扎根您现在不仅可以
take screw some double values but also
取一些双精度值，但也
big decimal values and beginning your
大十进制值并开始您的
values some of you might find helpful is
某些人可能会发现有用的价值观是
lexicographical array comparisons and
字典数组比较和
Java you array
Java数组
these also have intrinsic support so
这些也有内在的支持，所以
they go nice and fast on processors for
他们在处理器上运行得很好并且很快
concurrent programming there been some
并发编程中有一些
updates there for timeouts for
在那里更新超时
completable future and if you do rocket
未来的发展，如果你做火箭
science kind of concurrency stuff
科学类的并发东西
they're interesting things invar handled
他们是invar处理的有趣的事情
that are on par with the features in c++
与c ++中的功能相当
Atomics so in summary there's
原子，所以总的来说
fundamental changes coming in jdk 9 with
jdk 9中的基本变化
modularity but there are a lot of other
模块化，但还有很多其他
features coming too including completing
功能也包括完成
planned work on project coin and project
项目硬币和项目的计划工作
lambda and these features are meant to
lambda和这些功能旨在
support long term evolution and help
支持长期发展并提供帮助
ease transitions to new releases over
简化向新版本的过渡
time if you want to find out what's
时间，如果你想找出是什么
happening you can follow along on open
发生的事情，你可以跟随开放
JDK
JDK
and the EA bills are available now for
现在可以使用EA帐单了
your evaluation so with that I'll take
您的评估，以便我接受
some questions for a minute or two this
一两分钟的一些问题
is a URL to the slides you can also
是幻灯片的网址，您也可以
tweet questions to this hashtag and
向这个标签发布问题，并
please make sure to download the jk9
请确保下载jk9
builds for evaluation thank you question
建立评估谢谢你的问题
the question is is the o for the house
问题是房子的o
that does it use a perfect hash for the
它为它使用完美的哈希
of I don't believe it does but that'd be
我不相信会这样，但是那会是
an excellent question to ask it
一个很好的问题要问
Stewart's session later in the later in
斯图尔特在晚些时候的会议
that conference
那次会议
so the question was about the the higher
所以问题是关于更高
plane characters and strings is not
平面字符和字符串不是
going to be changing given the new
鉴于新的变化
internal representation so the aunt
内部代表，所以阿姨
dancer is no it is as inconvenient or as
舞者是不便还是不便
inconvenient
不方便
today as it was was was previously to
今天是以前
get the surrogate Paris well the the
得到代理巴黎很好
speed of the relative speed different
速度相对速度不同
operations of work was done to try to
工作运作是为了尝试
not have gratuitous degradation to
没有不必要的退化
performance so there may be some
性能，所以可能会有一些
operations that are slow with the new
新产品运行缓慢
encoding but others that are faster
编码，但其他更快
different people want different things
不同的人想要不同的东西
yep
是的
so so the question was could you get
所以问题是你能得到吗
around a diamond with non notable types
围绕非显着类型的钻石
by using a specific type argument yes
通过使用特定的类型参数是
you could certainly basically not not
你当然可以基本上不
used diamond or try to influence the
二手钻石或尝试影响
inference that was going on to make it
正在进行的推理
the notable instead but since the
值得注意的是，但由于
purpose so that is is a fallback but we
目的，所以这是一个后备，但我们
did want to support it
确实想支持它
the inference in this case where nothing
在这种情况下的推论
bad actually happened with it in notable
实际发生的不好是值得注意的
types so the question is what's the
类型，所以问题是什么
difference between the EI and ei with
EI和EI之间的差异
the latest jigsaw so the jigsaw feature
最新的拼图，所以拼图功能
is currently and has been in the
目前且一直在
mainline ei bills for some time the
主线EI账单一段时间
jigsaw team they do some more
拼图团队，他们还有更多工作要做
exploratory work in the a builds and
探索性工作
then once that stabilize it gets put
然后一旦稳定下来
into the into the jigsaw train and then
进入拼图火车，然后
once that's stabilized they put it into
一旦稳定下来，他们就把它放进去
the other ei bills right it is more
其他EI账单对吧
bleeding-edge it's a little more
流血的边缘多一点
experimental
实验性的
the question was the with the security
问题是安全性
updates and the using the eliminated
更新和使用消除
ranked libraries in jk9 I don't know
我不知道jk9中的排名库
offhand but Sean Mullan and the other
但副手肖恩·穆兰（Sean Mullan）和其他人
people on the security lives team will
安全生命团队中的人员将
will be able to answer that question
将能够回答该问题
handily at their bluff and I think one
轻而易举地虚张声势，我认为
more question
更多问题
so the question was on backwards
所以问题在向后
compatibility so are you asking about J
兼容性，所以您是否询问J
Deborah scan or which which are you
黛博拉扫描或你是谁
asking about
询问
I'm not sure understanding your question
我不确定您的问题
I think I'll answer it off offline here
我想我会在这里离线回答
so so thank you for coming
所以谢谢你的光临